lan Clark

Email: ianclark226@gmail.com Phone: 484-574-3255

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/ianclark226/ Portfolio: https://ianclark-fullstackportfolio.netlify.app

Github: https://github.com/ianclark226

Fullstack Developer with several years of experience in Graphic Design and a background in Game Design. Proficient with a wide array of scripting languages, databases, and multimedia web tools. Adapts well when working with diverse teams that have strong missions of implementing new projects or designs in web development.

TECHNICAL // SKILLS

<u>UX/UI</u>: Photoshop, Adobe Suite, Lightroom, Kodak Digital Print Production(DP2), Premiere Pro, Unity3D, Maya, and Cinema 4D.

<u>Web Development;</u> Express.js, Node.js, React.js, Redux, JavaScript ES5/ES6, Handlebars.js, JQuery, JSON, AJAX, HTML, CSS, Heroku, REST APIs, Bootstrap, Sequelize, Wordpress, PHP, Python, Django, AWS, Docker. Databases: MongoDB, MySQL, and Postgres.

Miscellaneous: Windows, Git/Github, Google Sheets, Google Suite, Microsoft Suite, Jira, Bitbucket.

APPLICATIONS

Billboard Tracking System: https://billboard-tracker.onrender.com/

- An application that allows users to see available Billboard space demographically in the area of Philadelphia.
- I was responsible for the Sequelize data and react.js.
- Technologies Used: HTML, Foundation CSS, Javascript, API, AJAX, React, mySQL, and Sequelized.

Game-Shop: https://django-react-fullewebsite-production.up.railway.app/

- An application that allows the user to buy games and get them shipped to you and leave reviews.

 Admin access can add products as well as remove and give access to other accounts.
- This is a Full Stack application that I have created.
- Technologies Used: React, Redux, Bootstrap, Django, Postgres, and AWS.

EXPERIENCE

Agile5 Technologies, Fairmont, WV (Remote) | Junior Software Developer/Data Integrator 9/2021- Present

- Developed company UI as well as deployments on AWS.
- Worked with the company's stack of React.js, Postgres, Django, and Docker.
- Create with mapping raw XML data from police reports into our person code mapping tool.
- Test and Deploy Data adapters for agencies to use with new data.
- Obtained a Secret Security Clearance for government contracting work.

Elroi LLC, Detroit, MI (Remote) | Fullstack Internship

9/2020- 12/2020

- Designed Login and Customer Portal page using HTML, CSS, Javascript, and React.js.
- Worked on the company's front end interface and backend database with Wordpress and PHP.

Barksdale School Portraits, Aston, PA | Photo Editor / Designer

8/2016- 9/2017

- Provided photo enhancements such as color correction, cropping, and removing glass glare.
- Manipulated exposure, shadows, and highlights with senior shoots, high school sports teams and class groups ensuring consistency of photos.
- Designed banners and composites to print and send to schools.

EDUCATION

University of Pennsylvania, LPS, Philadelphia, PA

• Certificate, An intense 24-week program dedicated to designing and building web applications.

Wilmington University, New Castle, DE

• B.S. Degree Game Design and Development